Preliminary Inventory to the Ray M. Hudson Papers, 1922-1957
Hoover Institution Archives
Ray M. Hudson Papers,
1922-1957
62013
Hudson, Ray M.
6 manuscript boxes. (2.5 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Letters, pamphlets, clippings, and other printed matter, relating to American industry, simplification of industrial practice, the public life of Herbert Hoover, and the 1928, 1932, and 1936 presidential campaigns.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Access Points
Hoover, Herbert, 1874-1964.; United States. Dept. of Commerce.; Presidents--United States--Election--1928.; Presidents--United States--Election--1932.; Presidents--United States--Election--1936.; Simplification in industry.; Standardization--United States.; United States--Industries.; United States--Politics and government.; New England Council. Industrial Committee.
Biography
Chief, Division of Simplified Practice, United States Department of Commerce, 1926.
Container List
- Clippings of Herbert Hoover and family, 1928 - 1929 August. Includes printed articles (Box 1.)
- Clippings (Box 2.)
- Printed articles and speeches by Ray M. Hudson re industry, labor, etc. - Hoover Commerce and Presidential period
- Miscellaneous pamphlets (Box 3.)
- Clippings and articles - Hoover Commerce and Presidential period
- Clippings and articles - Hoover Presidential period (Box 4.)
- Miscellaneous clippings and pamphlets
- Article, "Industry, Labor and the Public" by Ray M. Hudson (Box 5.)
- Correspondence and comments by leading businessmen, 1938
- Miscellaneous pamphlets
- Political clippings, 1936-1937 (Box 6.)
- Articles re simplified practice in industry
- New England Council - Report of Industrial Committee, 1936
- Political clippings, 1935-1937. See Hoover files